Statehood Commission
DC Public Library, Special Collections
Statehood Commission Records
1788-1994
DC Public Library, Special Collections
22 linear feet;51 boxes
048
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series 1: Administrative, 1986-1994
  - 501(c)(3) application [incomplete], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ad hoc committee report, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Address Lists, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Administrative consultant, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administrative materials, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Administrative materials, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Administrative materials, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Administrative materials, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual report, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Appointment list, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Awards, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - By-laws, July 22 1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - By-laws, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - By-laws/amendments, April 14 1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - By-laws - article IV - section 2, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - By-laws - final draft, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - By-laws - inactive members, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - By-laws - officers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - By-laws - revised, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - By-laws - revised, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - By-laws - revised, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - By-laws - setup, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Capital Services proposal, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Central committee meeting schedule and agenda, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Commission activities, June 1987-June 1988 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Commission activities, July-August 1989 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Commission activities, September 1989 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Commission activities, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Commission Report to D.C. Counsel, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Commission Status, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Commissioners, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Commissioners - appointment materials, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Commissioner mailings, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Commissioner mailings, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Commissioner mailings, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Commissioner materials - Peter Schott, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Commissioner review of public relations proposal - Josephine Butler, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Commissioner review of public relations proposal - Peter Schott, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Consultant resumes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Contracts - Bobby William Austin (Research), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Contracts - Yvonne Bess, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Contracts - Lisa Fadden, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Contracts - Harrison Institute (legal services), 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Contracts - Harrison Institute contract modification, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Contracts - Harrison Institute, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Contracts - Harrison Institute, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Contracts - Harrison Institute, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Contracts - In the Public Eye Productions, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Contracts - KNETWork International Corporation, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Contracts - NAPA, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Contracts - Richard Montgomery Graphic Designs, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Contracts - Peter Winch, January 5 1989 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Contracts Evaluation Committee, August 19 1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - D.C. government agency research list, Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Francis McGinnis and Rees Inc. proposal, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Fundraising, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Handwritten notes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Harrison Institute proposal [analysis of legal and constitutional issue], June 14 1984 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Harrison Institute activities, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Harrison Institute proposal, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Information mailers, Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Internships, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Lists of contacts, Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - List of delegates [unknown], Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Liberty Bell express riders, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Mailing lists, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Meeting announcements, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - NAPA proposal - transition to statehood, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - NAPA workplan, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - New member package originals, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Charles Q Pearson Proposal, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Program Committee, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Program of work, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Proposals, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Request for Proposal (RFP) CI-1-88 [public relations], 1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - RFP CI-1-88 - Anderson Communications response, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - RFP CI-1-88 - David Apter response for public relations campaign, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - RFP CI-2-88 [educational video], 1988 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - RFP CI-2-99 - David Apter response for educational video, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - RFP CI-2--88 - General Investment Concepts Incorporated, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - RFP CI-2-88 - General responses, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - RFP C-2-88 - Harrison Institute response, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - RFP CI-2-88 - Maguire Reeder response, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - RFP CI-3-88, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - RFP CI-3-88 - Harrison Institute response, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - RFP CI-3-88 - RBS Inc. Response, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - RFP CI-3-88 - Cost Proposal - We Want Work, October 14 1988 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - RFP CI-1-89 [Polling Survey], 1989 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - RFP CI-1-89 - Grasman Health and Business Research response, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - RFP CI-1-89 - Unicorn Corporation, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - RFP CI-1-94, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - RFP CI-1-94 - shell version, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - RFP CI-1-94 - extension, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - RFP CI-1-94 - Edward Guinan response, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - RFP CI-3-94 - (marketing and T.V. spots), 1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - RFP CI-3-94 - Proposal in response from Statehood Solidarity Committee to produce T.V. spots, September 9 1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Resolution, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Resolutions - public relations firms, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Resume for commission positions, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Retreat, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Retreat, January 12 1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Sign-in sheet [unknown event], Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Statehood activities, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Statehood activities, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Statehood activities, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Statehood activities, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Statehood activities, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Stationary and logo, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Stationary - D.C. Statehood Party, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Time and effort reports, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Time and effort reports - Dedre Feerdon, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Time and effort reports - Edward Guinan, August 15-31 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Time and effort reports Peter Winch, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Travel, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Travel regulations, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - VCR, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Vacancies and possible candidates, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Volunteers, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Work schedules, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Series 2: Financial, ca. 1978-1995
  - Account of expenditures, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Appropriations Act, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Appropriations Act, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Apter and Associates billing, February 6 1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Bill 8-150 - FY 1990 Budget Request Act (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Budget financial issues, 1986-1991 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Budget 1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Budget call, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Budget, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Budget request - operating, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Budget - proposed, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Budget reduction memoranda, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Budget, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Budget - projected, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Budget reconciliation, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Budget structure, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Budget call, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Budget - statehood video, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Budget call, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Budget call, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Budget funding levels, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Budget presentation, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Budget testimony - Josephine Butler and Arrington Dixon, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Budget, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Budget, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Budget - Supplemental Request - Testimony of N. Sloan, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence [re financial matters], 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence with controller, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Office of the Budget, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Office of the Budget, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Office of the Budget, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Office of the Budget, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Procurement Practices Act of 1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Candidate waiver forms, Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Expenses, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Expenses - convention, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Expenses - printing, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Expenses - convention exhibitor services, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Expenses, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Financial review process, March 6 1986 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - {Financial working papers], 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Funding memoranda, February 9 1990 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Funding, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - GAO briefing report to Congress - financial status of D.C., June 1994 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Harrison Institute billing, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Invoices, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Invoice and receipt - Washington Press, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Payment vouchers, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Payment vouchers and financial background, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Payment vouchers and journals, October 1986-October 1987 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Payment vouchers and journals, November 1987-October 1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Payment vouchers, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Payment vouchers, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Payment vouchers, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Payment vouchers, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Payment vouchers, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Payment vouchers, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Payment vouchers and receipts, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Payment vouchers and journal, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Payment vouchers and journal, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Procurement guidelines, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Procurement policy - draft, Undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Procurement policy - final, Undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Revenues and expenditures statement, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Revenues and expenditures statement - Statehood constitutional convention, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Revenues and expenditures statement, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Revenues and expenditures statement, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Statehood constitutional convention financial report, 1982-1985, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Statement of disbursement - D.C. government, Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Statement of funds spent, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Tax exempt status, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Travel and expense and related regulations, Undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Treasurer's report, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Treasurer's report and reconciliation, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Treasurer's report and reconciliation, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Treasurer's report and reconciliation, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Treasurer's report and reconciliation, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Series 3: Meetings, 1978-1995
  - Meeting minutes/agendas/background materials (non-inclusive), December 11 1978 - October 2 1986 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Meeting minutes/agendas/background materials, November 6 1986 - November 5 1987 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Meeting minutes/agendas/background materials, December 3 1987 - April 20 1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Meeting minutes/agendas/background materials, April 22 1988 - September 1 1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Meeting minutes/agendas/background materials, October 6 1988 - December 19 1988 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Meeting minutes/agendas/background materials, December 15 1988 - May 4 1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Meeting minutes/agendas/background materials, May 4 1989 - December 15 1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Meeting minutes/agendas/background materials, March 23 1990 - January 5 1995 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Series 4: Topics, 1788, 1941, 1968, 1980-1993
  - ANC 1C, Undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - ANC - endorsements of Statehood Commission, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - ANC information, 1987-1989 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Adams-Morgan, 1980-1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Ad Hoc committee report, Undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Against statehood, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Average expenditure per pupil in elementary schools by neighborhood income group, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Bibliography - new federalism, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Bibliographies, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Bibliographies, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Brookings Institute, Undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Campaign contribution limitations, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Campaign finance, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Census of retail trade, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Cession acts - Maryland and Virginia, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Chadha case, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Children's Crusade for Freedom, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Citizens for New Columbia - Matsimela Mapfumo statement, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Citizens for New Columbia - Plan of Act, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - A Citywide Statehood Plan of Action: Working Draft, March 12 1993 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Commission - set-up authority, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Common Cause, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Community and public support, Undated (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Commuter tax, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Compact Commission blueprint, Undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Comprehensive Plan for the National Capital, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Congressional Enabling Acts and Acts of Administration - John Mandler Memoranda, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Congressional Enabling Acts and Acts of Administration - John Mandler Memoranda, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Constitution of State of New Columbia, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Constitution of State of New Columbia, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Constitution of State of New Columbia, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Constitution of the District of Columbia - proposed amendments, April 15 1985 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Constitution for the State of New Columbia, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Constitution for the State of New Columbia - Approval Act, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Constitution for the State of New Columbia - Approval Act, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Constitution for the State of New Columbia - Bill in the House of Representatives, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Constitutions of the State of New Columbia - Differences in, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Convention trip list - Ward 7, Undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Council resolution - "No taxation without Representation", 1993 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Court Case "National Capital Religious Liberty and Academic Freedom Act", 1988 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Credit rating, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - D.C. before and after school care program - Virginia Reid, Undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - D.C. Code - Commission authority, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Commission for Women Hall of Fame Ceremony, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Humanities Council, 1989, 1986-1990 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition - membership, July 27 1987 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition - membership, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Statehood Constitutional Convention - Delegates, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Statehood Constitutional Convention - Initiative, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Statehood Constitutional Convention Preparatory Seminar, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Statehood Commission Amendment Act of 1994 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Statehood Forum and Organizing Committee, Undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Statehood Inaugural Committee, December 1990 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Statehood Party Meeting announcement, April 1979 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Statehood Party Platform, Undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Statehood Party Steps to Revitalize, April 2 1989 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Statehood Party Resolution on military spending, Undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Democratic Party - proposed party plank regarding statehood, Undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Disenfranchisement research, Undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - District Clause - Federalist No. 43, 1788 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - District Clause in Constitution - P.L. 93-198, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Economic Facts, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Elections, 1980-1992 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Election, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Election Guide - Washington Star News, October 24 1974 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Election results, September 11 1990 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Election results, November 6 1990 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Emergency Leadership meeting, May 6 1992 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Federal payment to District, Undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Festivals and events, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Facilitating the transition from city to State memoranda, Undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Fire Department - 1987 The 51-Star Flag History (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - FOIA request, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Friends or Meridian Hill Inc., 1991 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Funding for Congressional representatives, May 19 1989 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - George Washington University, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - History - D.C. Statehood Commission, Undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Julius Hobson - Celebration, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Hobson Tribute, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Home Rule analysis, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Home Rule - D.C. Self Government and Government Reorganization Act, February 8 1974 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Homestead Housing-Lottery, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Jesse Jackson - Campaign, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Jesse Jackson - Clippings, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Jesse Jackson - Shadow Senatorship, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Jesse Jackson - Statement on D.C. Statehood, April 1 1993 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Jamaica partnership, Undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - King Birthday, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - LVT, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Land grants to new States, Undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Lobby requirements - federal and D.C., January 19 1981 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Long term strategic planning for Proposition One, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Lorton and related issues, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Maps from Comprehensive Plan for National Capital Area, 1974, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Marie-Reed Community Center, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Hilda Mason; Campaign decision, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Hilda Mason; Committee to Re-elect, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Hilda Mason; Election board, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Mayoral politics, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - NRDC - Common Cause - Department of Public Works - Solid Waste Management Plan, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - National Bicentennial Writing Competition, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - National Capital Service Area, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - National Capital services director, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - National Constitution Bicentennial events, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Newsletter materials, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Non-partisan elections, Undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Obsolete constitutional provisions, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Organizations supporting statehood, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Origins of the federal city, Undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Outline for discussion - Emergency Leadership Meeting, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Parking case, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Peace Train, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Periodical listing, Undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Persian Gulf War comments - Eleanor Holmes Norton remarks, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Proclamation - Respiratory Health Awareness Month, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Program Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Promotions Committee, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - "Questions and answers on National Community Health Service" - Undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Rainbow Coalition, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - John Ray - Christmas Carol, Undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Re-delegation of local government powers, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Referral of proposed legislation, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Referral of proposed legislation, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Referral of court cases, 1982-1985 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Referral of court cases, 1982-1985 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Referral of court cases, 1982-1985 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Referral of court cases, 1982-1985 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Referral of court cases, 1982-1985 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Referral of court cases, 1982-1985 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Republic National Committee delegates list, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Republic National Committee delegates list, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Republic National Convention, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Republican party issues, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Republican Study Committee, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Resolutions passed at 1989 convention (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Resolution - Julius Hobson, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Resolution - Puerto Rico Statehood, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Resources for Community Change Inc., Undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Revenue D.C., 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Revision of U.S. Code memoranda June 7, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Robeson Friendship Society, 1988-1992 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Robeson program on statehood, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Roster of events, May-19 - June 1987 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Roundtable on employment, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Shadow representatives in Congress - Congressional Research Service (CRS) Report, January 1 1991 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Shadow senators - notes and research, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Shapiro tract - Adams-Morgan, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - State government reorganization, 1970s-1980s (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - State government reorganization, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - State government reorganization - Expert list, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - State government reorganization - State charts, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - State government reorganization - Transition blueprint, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Statehood awards ceremony, December 1988 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Statehood commissioners, Undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Statehood Compact Commission - Background, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Shadow delegates proposal - May 9, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Statehood congressional delegation and ANC swearing-in, Undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Statehood: current readings, 1910, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Statehood history and background, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Statehood initiative, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Statehood mission team, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Statehood motorcade, Undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Statehood questions, Undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Statehood strategy and timetable, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Status of District Environmental Master Plan, August 8 1978 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Statehood congressional delegation and ANC Swearing-In, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Statehood Commission [Statement of Purpose], Undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Statehood Party Central Committee, January 18 1989 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Statehood summit, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 11)